Stefan Speter

stefanspeter26@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/stefan-speter/ | https://stefanspeter.fr/

RESUME OBJECTIVE

Web developer with over 3 years of experience working internationally. I'm seeking a position as a developer or a project manager where I could leverage my skills in Drupal, VueJS, php, Javascript, HTML/CSS/Sass and serve as a strong asset to the company.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

AKABIA, Lille, France

Intern Drupal Web Developer & Project Management Assistant

September 2020 - Present

- Worked as a full stack developer for over 20 projects using Drupal 7 to Drupal 9 for national and foreign clients.
 - https://en.unesco.org/inclusivepolicylab/(Drupal7),
 https://en.unesco.org/silkroad/(Drupal8),
 https://emploi.isagri.fr/ (Drupal 9).
- Collaborated with marketing and project management teams to deliver projects on-time and with the highest standard.
- Acted as the lead developer and worked with web integrator for three projects. I led the full lifecycle of the project from managing the tasks and creating the work environment to put into production.
- Worked on intranet websites with very technical demand.
- Assisted the Chief Technology Officer in managing clients by coordinating regular calls to gather requirements and review project statuses.

HB Digit, Lille, France

Intern Drupal Web Developer

August 2019 - August 2020

- Worked as a backend developer to create an e-commerce Drupal 8 website https://www.lashootingbox.com/
- Used and learned Flutter for an intern app.

EDUCATION

EFFICOM University, Lille, France

Master's degree, Digital Project Management

2019 - 2022

Bachelor's degree, Digital Project Management

Coursework: Agile project management, UX/UI design, change management, digital transformation and entrepreneurship

Certificates: JavaScript Algorithms, Data Structure and Responsive Web Design delivered by freeCodeCamp. Currently working to pass the Professional Scrum Product Owner delivered by scrum.org.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Operating Systems: Windows, Mac OS, Linux, Android, iOS, Chrome OS

Programming: Drupal 7/8/9, HTML5/CSS3/Sass, VueJS, Php (Symfony/Composer), Twig, JavaScript, jQuery, GraphQL, Git, SQL

Stefan Speter

stefanspeter26@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/stefan-speter/ | https://stefanspeter.fr/

LANGUAGE | INTERESTS

Fluent in English and French

Interests: Finance, Team Sports, Fitness, Video Games, Chess, Travelling